Blood Vessel is a horror, fantasy, war film directed by Justin Dix.
Near the end of World War II, the survivors of a torpedoed
hospital ship cling to life aboard a crowded lifeboat.
With no food, water, or shelter, all seems lost – until an eerily silent German
minesweeper drifts ominously towards them, giving them one last chance at survival.
As our motley crew explores the ship, it becomes all too clear that
some diabolical fate has befallen its German crew.
The mystery only deepens when they encounter a young Romanian girl, apparently the sole
survivor, who leads them to a locked room in the bowels of the vessel.
Nathan Sinclair, played by Nathan Phillips.
Jane Prescott, played by Alyssa Sutherland.
Captain Malone, played by Robert Taylor.
Lydell Jackson, played by Christopher Kirby.
Alexander Teplov, played by Alex Cooke.
Jimmy Bigelow, played by Mark Diaco.
Blood Vessel is a 2019 horror film that was filmed in Melbourne, Australia.
The film was directed by Justin Dix and written by Dix and Jordan Prosser.
It stars Alyssa Sutherland, Robert Taylor, Nathan Phillips,
Christopher Kirby, John Lloyd Fillingham, and Alex Cooke.
The film premiered as a closing night film at 2019 FilmQuest in Provo, Utah, where it was nominated for eleven
awards, winning for Best Art Department, Best Costume, and Best Supporting Actress for Sutherland.
The film was released on 21 July 2020 via video-on-demand service Shudder.
The film explores themes of world war ii, shipwreck survivors, haunted ship.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.